He'll do anything to give her a baby... even murder.
Ultimate Deception is a tv movie, thriller film directed by Richard A. Colla.
Terry is desperate to start a family.
Unable to bear her own children, she must rely on
adoption, which proves to be a difficult task.
Terry Cuff, played by Yasmine Bleeth.
Bobby Woodkin, played by Richard Grieco.
Andy McThomas, played by Gordon Michael Woolvett.
Cloë, played by Robin Brûlé.
Dana Ballard, played by Sabrina Grdevich.
Elaine McThomas, played by Nola Augustson.
Ultimate Deception (also known as Ultimate Betrayal) is a 1999
made-for-television drama film directed by Richard A.
Colla and starring Yasmine Bleeth and Richard Grieco, who were living
together in real life at the time the film was produced.
The tone is intense.